Contact

joelpalford@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/joel-alford-372134113 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Public Speaking
Healthcare

Certifications

SAMA (Satori Alternatives to Managing Aggression)

Stroke Scale

Registered Nurse

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

Joel Alford

BSN, RN, CMSRN

Flower Mound, Texas

Summary

Passion, care, and dedication drive me to become the best nurse possible. I have joined the exceptional team of nurses at Medical City Lewisville providing me the opportunity to learn and grow as a professional nurse while gaining valuable experience and certifications to propel me further in my nursing career.

Experience

Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas) 2 years 9 months

Post Anesthesia Care Nurse October 2019 - Present (9 months) Lewisville, TX

Charge Nurse

October 2017 - October 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Lewisville, Texas

Tele/onc med-surg

Grace Christian Academy
Substitute Teacher
August 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)

Flower Mound, Texas

Pensacola Christian College

3 years 9 months

Stage Crew

September 2013 - May 2017 (3 years 9 months)

Proclaim Team Student Leader November 2014 - December 2016 (2 years 2 months)

Lina T. Ramey & Associates, Inc. (LTRA) Vaccum truck operator and utility marker

Page 1 of 2

June 2013 - August 2013 (3 months)

Dallas

Education

Pensacola Christian College

Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2013 - May 2017)

Grace Christian Academy

Diploma with Honors, Honors/Regents High School/Secondary Diploma Program · (2009 - 2013)